smnweekly.com 2014-03-07

# Animation, Celebrity News, Cartoons, Games, Personality Quiz | Liquid Generation

This statement describes the privacy policy of LiquidGeneration, Inc. ("LiquidGeneration") for its website, Liquidgeneration.com. It applies only to Liquidgeneration.com, so if you visit other sites linked to Liquidgeneration.com, you should review the privacy policies of those sites. Also, this privacy policy does not apply to Liquidgenerations’s practices for gathering information offline or at other sites that it may own or operate. Also, LiquidGeneration reserves the right to update this policy at any time without notice, so we suggest that you occasionally review it. 

#### Information collected by Liquidgeneration.com:

##### Personal information.

You do not have to provide personal information to access or browse Liquidgeneration.com. However, we may ask you to provide personal information in connection with various opportunities and activities available at Liquidgeneration.com. By "personal information," we mean information that is identifiable to you. Personal information requested might include, for example, your email address, or, where identifiable to you, other information such as your age, zip code, gender and/or ethnicity.   
Automatic or Navigational Information. When you visit Liquidgeneration.com, we capture certain information automatically (even if you do not provide us with personal information), including your Internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, time and date of access and pages accessed. This "automatic" information, however, may become identifiable to you – and therefore "personal information"-- if you provide us with your email address or other personal information with which such "automatic or navigational" information then becomes programmatically associated. 

##### Information Collected by Cookies.

We use cookies to collect information about how visitors use Liquidgeneration.com and what pages and features visitors find more or less interesting. 

#### Ownership of Submissions

Videos, photos, emails, letters and any other information, uploaded, emailed, File Transported, or otherwise communicated to LiquidGeneration Inc., its employees and staff, or any agents or representatives of LiquidGeneration Inc, including writers for the LiquidGeneration Blogs and Mailroom become the property of LiquidGeneration Inc., and they will have the right to use them free of charge, and in any manner and in any medium, forever and throughout the world. This means that submissions might appear in publications including, but not limited to, a book, newsletter or on a LiquidGeneration Inc. web site. If you do not want your submissions to become the property of LiquidGeneration Inc., please do not submit, upload, email or otherwise communicate them to us. 

#### Who else has access to the information you provide?

Except as provided below, we do not transfer information to third parties in a manner that identifies you. Thus for example, we would not sell information that includes your email address. We do transfer to third parties and/or release to the public certain aggregate information (for example about the visiting habits of our visitors generally or of groups of our visitors), but that information will not contain information that identifies you.   
There are three groups of exceptions to our policy of not transferring personal information to third parties: 

**1.** Liquidgeneration.com Service Providers. Third parties who provide hosting services or other day-to-day services that make possible the operation of Liquidgeneration.com may have access to information that you provide to the extent they require access to our databases to service LiquidGeneration and Liquidgeneration.com.

**2.** Liquidgeneration.com’s Security. We reserve the right to release personal information when we believe that the law requires us to do so or when we believe it is necessary to protect and/or enforce the rights, property interests, or safety of LiquidGeneration.com, our users or others.

**3.** Reorganization or Sale of LiquidGeneration;Affiliates. LiquidGeneration may transfer personal information to any entity controlling LiquidGeneration, to any entity that LiquidGeneration controls or to any entity that is under common control with LiquidGeneration. In the event that LiquidGeneration is merged with or becomes part of another organization, or in the event that LiquidGeneration is sold or it sells all or substantially all of its assets, the information you provide will be one of the transferred assets.

#### Children and LiquidGeneration.com:

LiquidGeneration has no intention of collecting any personally identifiable information from individuals under thirteen years of age. 

#### Security:

#### Third Party Advertising:

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy). 

#### Third Party Cookies:

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Liquidgeneration.com provides you the following options for modifying or removing information our databases: 

**1.** Click the Unsubscribe Link at the bottom of every newsletter.

**3.** Send a letter to the following address:

LiquidGeneration, Inc.   
8750 Wilshire Blvd  
Suite 301  
Beverly Hills, CA 90211

 **4.** Telephone us at: 310-289-7877

#### Questions?

you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement, the practices of LiquidGeneration, or your dealing with our web site, please contact us.
